(Sheldon:)...could be construed as offensive.
(Sheldon:)And I would like to offer you
my sincerest apology.
(Alex:)Thank you, Dr. Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Additionally, you should know
that the university has mandated...
(Sheldon:)...that I take an online sexual harassment
seminar so that this sort of thing...
(Sheldon:)...doesn't happen in the future.
(Alex:)- Okay.
- Now, unfortunately...
(Sheldon:)...my time is much too valuable
to waste on nonsense like this...
...so I'm going to need you
to take it for me.
Oh, and you'd better ace it,
they're pretty mad.
(Penny:)- I was thinking about that stuff with Alex...
- Would you stop worrying about that?
I can't help it. But I figured
I could sit around...
(Penny:)...and feel insecure, or
I could do something about it.
So, I got a course catalog at school
and looked at some of the science classes.